Guide to the Kilpatrick Collection of Cherokee Manuscripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Kilpatrick collection of Cherokee manuscripts
1870-1966
WA MSS S-2707
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
9.38
(23 boxes)
The Kilpatrick collection of Cherokee manuscripts consists of material created and accumulated by Jack Kilpatrick and Anna Gritts Kilpatrick, dating from the 1890s to the 1960s. The material, entirely in the Cherokee syllabary, documents vernacular literacy in the Cherokee language, the practice of traditional medicine, social aspects of Christian religion and church organizations, dates and circumstances of death, funerary practices, and other topics relating to the history and culture of the Oklahoma Cherokee in the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries. Medical formulae (also called prayers, incantations, conjurations, or sacred formulae) were collected from Cherokee practitioners by Jack Frederick and Anna Gritts Kilpatrick in the 1960s. Portions of these manuscripts have been published in English translation and/or transliterated Cherokee, and citations to published sources have been noted in the contents list.
Kilpatrick, Jack Frederick
Kilpatrick, Anna Gritts
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Alan Kilpatrick and Brick Row Book Shop on the Walter McClintock Memorial Fund and Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 1979-1983.
Kilpatrick, Jack Frederick
Jack Frederick Kilpatrick, 1915-1967, American folklorist and professor at Southern Methodist University in Dallas. Kilpatrick interviewed Cherokee folk healers in the 1960s and collected manuscripts relating to traditional medicine. His research with his wife Anna Grits Kilpatrick resulted in books including Friends of Thunder (1964), Walk in Your Soul (1965), Run Toward the Nightland (1967), and Notebook of a Cherokee Shaman (1970).
Kilpatrick, Anna Gritts
Anna Gritts Kilpatrick, American folklorist and wife of Jack Frederick Kilpatrick. Her research with her husband resulted in books including Friends of Thunder (1964), Walk in Your Soul (1965), Run Toward the Nightland (1967), and Notebook of a Cherokee Shaman (1970).
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Arrangement
Organized into groupings that reflect binders kept by the Kilpatricks. Arrangement as received by the library has been retained.
Scope and Contents
The Kilpatrick collection of Cherokee manuscripts consists of material created and accumulated by Jack Kilpatrick and Anna Gritts Kilpatrick, dating from the 1890s to the 1960s. The material, entirely in the Cherokee syllabary, documents vernacular literacy in the Cherokee language, the practice of traditional medicine, social aspects of Christian religion and church organizations, dates and circumstances of death, funerary practices, and other topics relating to the history and culture of the Oklahoma Cherokee in the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries. Medical formulae (also called prayers, incantations, conjurations, or sacred formulae) were collected from Cherokee practitioners by Jack Frederick and Anna Gritts Kilpatrick in the 1960s. Portions of these manuscripts have been published in English translation and/or transliterated Cherokee, and citations to published sources have been noted in the contents list.
Cherokee Indians; Cherokee Indians -- Economic conditions; Cherokee Indians -- Ethnobotany; Cherokee Indians -- History; Cherokee Indians -- Genealogy; Cherokee Indians -- Medicine; Cherokee mythology; Cherokee Indians -- Religion; Cherokee language -- Texts; Indians of North America -- Medicine; Cherokee Nation; United Keetoowah Band of Cherokee Indians in Oklahoma; Kilpatrick, Jack Frederick
- "Medicine Men of the Cherokees"
  Arrangement
  Not arranged in any particular order, as received in binders by the Beinecke Library.
  - "Medicine Men of the Cherokees Part II," Black notebook cover, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Wolf, Arch, Senior. Shopping list, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Scope and Contents
    "Arch Wolf Sen. Coll. 1885-1962"
  - Wolf, Arch, Senior. Names and death dates in 1918., after 1918 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Wolf, Arch, Senior. Names and death dates in 1898, 1900, after 1900 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Baseball positions and initials, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Verso: "Beginners Dept Centenary S. S. Mrs. R. V. Cooper - Treas"
  - List on a small card, with numbers, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Recto: financial list with names and numbers; verso: practice English handwriting, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Crawford, Ned. Autograph letter, signed, Braggs, OK, to Arch Wolf, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dates of death in 1919, after 1919 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Recto: grocery list; verso: Arrow Sales Service flyer advertising Central European Display Set and 300,000 Million Mark, German Currency, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Financial records including names and numbers, 1915 March (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Mary" (Meli Hidasgi). Letter regarding plans for Christmas, to Tsesini Awigadoga, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Genealogical notes or list of birth dates, after 1922 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    The number "2" is circled at the top of the page
  - Tsuwi Wadi. Letter, to unidentified recipient, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Recto: Note; verso: printed statistical tables that record financial contributions to missions, circa 1920 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Letter to "my brother" Jackson Standingdeer, 1936 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Funeral notice for a child of Tse:ghwisi, 1926 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #4
    Custodial History
    The source of the obituary notice in this folder, as well as unspecified others in the collection, is identified in a note by Jack Kilpatrick as Jennie Foster. Kilpatrick's note reads: "Echota funeral notices collection 1925-1946. Obtained from Mrs. Jennie Foster, June, 1963."
  - Funeral notice for a child of Dagv:wo:si, 1926 May 8 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #3
  - Funeral notice for V:wo:di Adi:dha:sgi, 1925 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #1
  - Funeral notice for a child of I:gagha'la, 1925 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #2
  - Funeral notice for a child of Diyo:hli, 1930 April 26 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #7.
  - Funeral notice for Gv:sgali:sgi Wahhya, 1930 September 3 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #8
  - Funeral notice for a female child of I:gagha'la, 1928 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #5
  - Funeral notice for a female child of Gv:lehwisgi, 1928 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #6
  - Funeral notice for Sa:li Ade:lanosda, 1930 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #9
  - Funeral notice for Tsa:ni Ginisv:ha, 1931 April 7 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #10
  - Funeral notice for a female child of Tsi:nagwa Wahhya, 1932 November 26 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #11
  - Funeral notice for Ge:hya'hi U:ghu:si, 1933 October 17 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #12
  - Funeral notice for Ghi:ladi Une:la, 1937 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #15; Signed "Dan Scott".
  - Funeral notice for a child of Ne:di Gwi:da (Ned Adair), 1934 August 16 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #13.
  - Funeral notice for a daughter of Wo:yi, 1935 April 19 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" # 14.
  - Recto: funeral notice for Si:na:sda Dhlvdi:sdi; verso: list of names and baseball positions, in English, 1938 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #18.
  - Funeral notice for a child of La:wani, 1938 December 29 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #19.
  - Funeral notice for Tsa:li Dhle:me:ha, 1937 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #16.
  - Funeral notice for a male child of Wadadu:ga Ali:tsa, 1937 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #17.
  - Letters and notes including practice in English and Latin writing, 8 pages, accompanied by an envelope, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - "Minutes of Cherokee Baptist Sunday School Association Held with 14-Mile Creek, Baptist Church," printed pamphlet in English with manuscript annotations in Cherokee, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Financial records, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Record of deaths with names and years spanning 1893-1898, after 1898 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Wolf, Arch, Sr. Records of deaths and of the sales of baskets, 5 pages, 1936-1941 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Annotated "Arch Wolf Sr. Book 1"
  - Fragment of a note, circa 1920 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Possibly identified by a number "14" at the top center of the page
  - List of five New Testament passage references, circa 1919 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Fragment, 1910? (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Found in proximity: a note by Jack Kilpatrick, "Tsegisini Awigadoga"
  - Hymn or Christian prayer, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Pages numbered "57" and "58"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Medical formula on penmanship paper, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Note on verso: "... from George B____"
  - Envelope: addressed to Josiah Glass, Vian, Oklahoma, 1938? (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Medical formula, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Watt Flute (Ugus' Gesguni). Medical formula notebook, 8 pages, with cover boards by Jack Kilpatrick, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Recto: funeral notice for Ade:lanosda Ganov:sanu:lv:hi; verso: envelope addressed to Mr. Jim Hair, Echota, Oklahoma., 1939 May 13 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #21
  - Funeral notice for a child of Disghwa:ni, 1939 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #20.
  - Funeral notice for Wadhi Dhla:me:ha, 1939 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Transcribed and translated in "Echota funeral notices" #22.
  - Sunday School notice, 1929 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Echota Sunday School notes, 6 pages, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Keetoowah Society notes, 1939 October (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Sunday School notes, 1935 September 9 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - List of Echota Church officers in English and Cherokee, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Echota Sunday School notes, 1930, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Echota Sunday school notes and financial records, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Sunday School texts, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - List of Sunday School members and financial records, undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
    One ledger sheet with printed page numbers 177 and 178.
  - Sunday School officer notes, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Echota Sunday School makes plans for the coming year, 1926 July 25 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    English translation published in Shadow p. 75.
  - Echota Sunday School decides to have a cake sale, 1929 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    English translation published in Shadow p. 76.
  - List of names, possibly attendance at Sunday School, undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
    Accompanied by note: "Jenny Foster Echota collection"
  - Practice handwriting, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Echota Sunday School note, 1928 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Sunday School financial notes, 1930 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Recto: Echota Church note, signed by Thomas Adair and Jim Hummingbird; verso: handwriting practice in English and Cherokee including the name Sam Jones Wolf, 1934 August 12 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Autograph letter, annotated "Barber, Okla.", 1933 November 18 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Autograph letter, annotated "Echota", 1933 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Echota Committee notes by Unesdala (secretary), 1928 February 12 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Record of committee officers, including Jim Hummingbird, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Recto: Christian prayer; verso: "Johnson Simmons", undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Notebook cover inscribed "kolvnv kawonu (raven duck)", undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Song, undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
    Six lines of song text, with the number 16 marking the upper right corner of the page
  - Arch Wolf medicine notebook and list of death dates, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    Accompanied by a note "Arch Wolf VIII"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
    Annotated with the number 41 on the top center of the sheet
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - List of purchases by a Union widow, 1867 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    English translation published in Shadow, pp. 20-21
  - Financial notes on the verso of a 1937 calendar, circa 1937 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Text referring to the "east" (North Carolina), undated (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Medical formula, written on a printed Notice of Taxes Due, Delaware County, 1930s (Box 2, Folder 91)
    Annotated "W. P. Brewer, Muskogee, Oklahoma"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
    Annotated with the number 4 on the top center and bottom center of the page
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
    Annotated by the number 55 at the bottom center, and 58 at the bottom right, of the page
  - Medical formula, on divining with a needle, undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Practice handwriting, undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - List of names and ages of the Wili Bolin family, 1939 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Sikwanid. Prayer., circa 1918 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    Accompanied by a note "Obtained August 1963"
  - Recto: medical formula. Verso: practice handwriting, alphabet, undated (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Recto: Tax assessment list filled out with the name Ed Handle of Marble, OK. Verso: medical formula, 1927 or 1928 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    Tax document of Ed Handle, Marble, Oklahoma
  - Charlie Jumper and Dan Standingdeer. Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 106)
    Accompanied by a note: "Tsali Usgasadi Dewi Awigadoga" (Charlie Jumper Dan Standingdeer)
  - Recto. Charlie Jumper. Medical formula. Verso: Notes in English regarding an order for clothing, undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Notes on an envelope, including "Stomp dance Sugar Mountain", undated (Box 1, Folder 108)
    "Stomp dance Sugar Mountain"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Recto: Medical formula. Verso: "Gal. III-10, here are cursed", undated (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Medical formula, annotated in English by Reverand William Jumper, "This is for conging [conjuring]", 2 pages, undated (Box 2, Folder 115)
    Annotated by Rev. William Jumper
  - Watt, Johnson (Tsanisini Wadi). Letter, illustrated with a small pencil drawing of two human figures, undated (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Recto: medical formula. Verso: letter from United States Department of the Interior to Sallie Killer Waters, 1938 April 26, circa 1938 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Standingdeer, Dave. letter, 4 pages, undated (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Standingdeer, Dave. Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Recto: Sunday, Jim. Medical formula. Verso: Standingdeer, Dave. Letter to Jim Sunday, Barber, Oklahoma, 1929 June 1, 1929, undated (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Medical formula, 2 pages, undated (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Recto: medical formula. Verso of envelope fragment addressed to Mr. John Johnson, 1928 February 7, circa 1928 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Medical formula, waterstained and blurred ink, undated (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Love letter, 1939 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    Translated in Shadow p. 88.
  - Unestala. Hymn book, 15 pages, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    Portions of this booklet are translated in Shadow pp. 78-80. In addition to hymns, the booklet includes grocery lists and other financial notes.
  - Letter relating to business or community organization, 1935 December 28 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Letter listing members of a community organization, 1938 August 25 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Letter relating to the Sycamore Tree Church, 1935 August 9 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Church collection record, 1938 August (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 135)
    Found in proximity to a note: "Nannie Hooper Collection"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Recto: Medical formula. Verso: Bank of Commerce deposit slip, Stilwell, Oklahoma, 1930s (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 145)
    Annotated "Lydia Smith, Peggs, Oklahoma"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Medical formula numbered 70, 40, 101, 102, 103, 90, 104, 121, and 131, two pages, undated (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Medical formula (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Index to medical formula in folder 157, undated (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Medical formula numbered 50, 100, 80, and 60, undated (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 2, Folder 166)
    Annoted with a presumably unrelated note in English: "Hello, Dakey Earbob, how are you getting along now."
  - Watt, Charley. Medical formula, 18 pages, undated (Box 2, Folder 167)
    Accompanied by a note: "Charley Watt Collection acquired from Thomas Hank, June 21, 1963"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 170)
- Notebook #4 "Uwedasat Collection"
  - Binder cover, labeled "Uwedasat Collection 4, I-XVII", undated (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Medical formula book XIV, undated (Box 3, Folder 172)
    "From a stationery tablet; pinholes on some items"
  - Medical formula book XV, undated (Box 3, Folder 173)
    "From a stationery tablet;" each sheet is marked "Adawi" [Adam]
  - Medical formula book XVI, undated (Box 3, Folder 174)
    "From a stationery tablet; pinned." Printed on tablet: image of the American flag and the phrase "Long may she wave."
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Mecial formula book XVII, undated (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Medical formula book I, "formulas obtained from Gunagilvdi", undated (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Medical formula book II, "formulas seemingly in hand of Tsowa Donisi", undated (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Medical formula book III, undated (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Medical formula book IV, undated (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Medical formula book V, undated (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Medical formula book VI, "formulas obtained from Adawi", undated (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Medical formula book VII, "formulas obtained from Guwi", undated (Box 3, Folder 182)
    "From small ledger"
  - Medical formula book VIII, undated (Box 3, Folder 183)
    "From stationery tablet; paginated and marked with +"
  - Medical formula book IX, undated (Box 3, Folder 184)
    "From stationery tablet; various numberings"
  - Medical formula book X, undated (Box 3, Folder 185)
    "From stationery tablet ... numbered"
  - Medical formula book XI, undated (Box 3, Folder 186)
    "From a small ledger"
  - Medical formula book XII, undated (Box 3, Folder 187)
    "From a stationery tablet; paginated"
  - Medical formula book XIII, undated (Box 3, Folder 188)
    Paper is marked "Clinton;" one sheet missing
- Notebook #6 "Uwedasat Collection"
  - Binder cover labeled "Uwedasat Collection 6 XXX", undated (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Notes on a printed page from a book of Gospels, circa 1905 (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Diga:sa:gwalv Di:ni:nv (Judge, Goingsnake District). Letter, Goingsnake District, to Digu:hledi:sgi Wa:dhi, 1897 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    A translation is published in Shadow pp. 47-48.
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Recto: medical formula. Verso: fragment of printed advertisement reading "hats, boots, groceries", undated (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Medical formula (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Recto: medical formula, Verso: list of figures and names in English, including "John", undated (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - Medical formula and songs, undated (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Medical formula and songs, undated (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - Letter with medical formula, 1902 November 20 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Medical formula on a printed form for recording lumber sawed in 1913, circa 1913 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - Bible study notes, undated (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - Medical formula (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Letter, undated (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 3, Folder 225)